ED.
I'm a little too curious.
I like it.
I'm losing track.
Promise me.
Yes, tell me you like me.
Always, always, always.
You have to give me love.
No, no, no.
You have to spoil me.
I don't want to look away.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
When the time is up, potassium wing, I don't want to fall behind too soon
I've been wondering about you for a long time.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Oh no, we've finished that, and we're almost ready to go on the air. It's 10 minutes before the show.
But Temptation, you're too lovely. I can't take my eyes off you.
Don't mind if I do.
Just watch.
I have to be cool to begin with Yes, let's call what's in front of us
# Sometimes it's sunny, sometimes it's cloudy, sometimes it's rainy at night, sometimes it's icy
What's with this weather?
I'm so excited
(I'm so excited for you)
I'm a little nervous.I am a little nervous.
There was a screen in the dressing room,
I could see that everyone was gathered there.
I will do my best!
The future that shines in the distance
I'm sure it will be for all of this.
I'm sure it will go around and around
I love you.
Clear!
Someone pull over.
Backstage.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Here you go, La La La La La.
Yee!
I'll say something. I can't say anything.
Either one. Either one. Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu.
Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu.
I like you.
Which is it?
Neither.
Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu.
Hey!
Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu.
What the hell?
I'm going to cock it twice.I'll rub it in twice.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
You're so cute.
I'm going to start something.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best!
Thank you for watching!
Calm down.
I can't do this.
Listen to my feelings.
Jingle, jangle, jangle, jangle.
I like what I feel
Turns into like
Don't just like like like.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're saying, "Kokoro kumonokumo
Kokoro kumonokumo together kumonokumo
Come on, do it! Come on!
Emotion back! Enjoy back!
Feeling good!
Yes!
Now dance our moves from now onCome on now, dance our moves!
Let's go!
Heart heart heart heart heart heart heart
Wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble
Cha-Yan-Kan-Nyon [CANVAS].
Thank you guys properly
I can't help it, I'm not leaving you
I can't part from you.
I can't put it into words
I can't say goodbye to you
I can't keep my hands off you
Give me a little tension, and something will come
I'll be waiting for you, and in the future, I'll be waiting for you.
I hope to see you in the future
I love you so much, select
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
Please keep it in your heart.
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
I can swear to the man that I'm too cute and worried about him.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
So cute, so cute, so cute, so cute, I love you
Adorable, adorable, adorable. I can't stop, Lara.
Hey, I don't believe you.You know what I don't believe in?
When you do, feel it. It's cute, cute, cute. It's too cute.
Adorable, adorable, adorable... and I can't wait to stretch out my hands. Anything.
Ketchup, corn on the cob, corn on the cob. Don't say it.
Hey, you happy?
Thank you.
Yes, so today was summery.
Thank you very much.
It was so hot.
I was the hottest.
Seriously, it was really hot.
It was hot like a waterfall.
It's like a natural waterfall.
It was like I was coming back from a waterfall.
It was hot.
But the fans were hot and it was a lot of fun.
Today was the hottest day.
Thank you very much.
Next year, by all means,
I would like to go in the summer,
I will do my best.
Bye bye.
I will do my best again.
Thank you very much.
Subscribe to our channel!Subscribe to my channel!
I don't know why, but when I smile, the world seems to glow.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, and somewhere else I'll get wet again.
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure there's someone crying somewhere, just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know the scenery in front of me, look, let's go wherever you want to go
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I'll paint a piece of the future
It's leading me to the future
Subtitle: Kyou
I can tell you now
Whenever you are lost, remember the reason for your tears
So that I can smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good bye, good bye, yesterday's me
After the rain, the town, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, Good bye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, in the city, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, I'm going to wear a rainbow dress
I'm wearing a rainbow dressI wear a rainbow dress.
Please subscribe to our channel!